A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Accessions 1997-2008, Record Group 4 FA785
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant and Grantee Files, 1971-1999; 2; 52.48 Cubic Feet
  - WNYC Foundation (D91101), 1990-1991 (Box 156, Folder 33)
  - WNYE, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 34)
  - Wayne Wolff (97-3321), 1996 (Box 156, Folder 35)
  - Women's Action Alliance, 1992 (Box 156, Folder 36)
  - Wood, Lucksinger and Epstein, 1990 (Box 156, Folder 37)
  - World Game Institute, 1994-1995 (Box 156, Folder 38-39)
  - World Press Freedom Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 156, Folder 40)
  - Wunderman Worldwide, 1991-1996 (Box 156, Folder 41)
  - WTTW Chicago, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 42)
  - WQED Pittsburgh, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 43)
  - W-X-Y-Z - General, 1990-1995 (Box 156, Folder 44-47)
  - Xerox, 1988-1993 (Box 156, Folder 48-51)
  - Yale University, 1976-1994 (Box 156, Folder 52-55)
  - Yeshiva University, 1994 (Box 156, Folder 56)
  - York University, 1992-1995 (Box 156, Folder 57-59)
  - Youth Policy Institute, 1990-1992 (Box 156, Folder 60)
  - Young and Rubicam, 1991-1996 (Box 156, Folder 61-62)
  - Young and Rubicam, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 1-2)
  - Zagat Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 157, Folder 3-4)
  - American Council on Germany, 1977 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Haskins Labs, 1976-1983 (Box 157, Folder 6-7)
  - South Africa - Divestment, 1984-1987 (Box 157, Folder 8-11)
  - Multimedia Corporation, 1996-1997 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Grants Index Card File - A-Z, 1984-1989
  - Grants Index Card File - A-Z, 1984-1989
  - Grants Index Card File - Miscellaneous, 1984-1989
- Henry Geller papers, 1967-1998; 3; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
  Biographical / Historical
  Henry Geller an attorney, law professor, and telecommunications advisor to the Markle Foundation has spent much of his career focused in the areas of telecommunications regulation and policymaking. Geller served the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) in various capacities for more than 20 years, including but not limited to serving as General Counsel in the mid-1960s and as an assistant to Dean Burch from 1969-1974 during Burch's chairmanship of the Commission. Geller also served as administrator of the National Telecommunications and Information Administration (NTIA) from 1978-1981.
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) Petitions, 1981-1985 (Box 77, Folder 1-6)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC) Petitions, 1981-1985 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Telecommunications Policy, 1981-1986 (Box 78, Folder 8-12)
  - Telecommunications Policy, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Fairness Doctrine, 1967-1994 (Box 79, Folder 14-18)
  - Multiple Ownership, 1980s (Box 80, Folder 19-22)
  - Political Broadcasts, 1972-1996 (Box 80, Folder 23-24)
  - Political Broadcasts, 1972-1996 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Prime Time Access Rule, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Process: Comparative, Auctions, EB Structure, 1980s (Box 81, Folder 27-28)
  - Telephones, Bell Operating Company, AT&T, 1980-1998 (Box 81, Folder 29-31)
  - Telephones, Bell Operating Company, AT&T, 1980-1998 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Public Interest - Broadcast Regulation, 1970s-1980s (Box 82, Folder 33-36)
  - Public Interest - Broadcast Regulation, 1970s-1980s (Box 83, Folder 37-38)
  - Cable Television, 1977-1994 (Box 83, Folder 39-41)
  - Cable Television, 1977-1994 (Box 84, Folder 42)
  - Children's Television, 1980-1995 (Box 84, Folder 43-44)
  - Cigarette Advertising, 1975-1990 (Box 84, Folder 45-46)
  - Communications Act, Regulation Policy, 1981-1998 (Box 84, Folder 47)
  - Communications Act, Regulation Policy, 1981-1998 (Box 85, Folder 48-49)
- Lloyd N. Morrisett Files, 1972-1998; 4; 9.58 Cubic Feet Seven standard record storage boxes and one letter document box.
  Bibliography
  Lloyd N. Morrisett served as President of the Markle Foundation from 1969-1998.
  - Lloyd N. Morrisett Chronological Files, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 1-5)
  - Lloyd N. Morrisett Chronological Files, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 6-10)
  - Lloyd N. Morrisett Chronological Files, 1997-1998 January (Box 86, Folder 11-15)
  - Children's Television Workshop (CTW) Files, 1992-1995 (Box 86, Folder 16-20)
    Primarily consists of correspondence and Board of Directors files and meeting records, as well as records of associated subcomittees.
  - Children's Television Workshop (CTW) Files, 1986-1995 (Box 87, Folder 1-24)
  - Children's Television Workshop (CTW) Files, 1990-1995 (Box 88, Folder 1-36)
  - Children's Television Workshop (CTW) Files, 1990-1995 (Box 89, Folder 1-21)
  - Memberships and Associations - SeniorNet, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Memberships and Associations - Oberlin, 1991-1995 (Box 90, Folder 2-8)
  - Memberships and Associations - National Research Council, 1994-1995 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Memberships and Associations - National Geographic Society, 1992-1993 (Box 90, Folder 10-12)
  - Memberships and Associations - Hoover Institution, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    Donated his papers to Hoover.
  - Memberships and Associations - Haskins Laboratories, 1992-1995 (Box 90, Folder 14-19)
  - Memberships and Associations - Darmouth Medical School Board of Overseers, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
  - Memberships and Associations - Council on Foreign Relations (CFR), 1992-1994 (Box 91, Folder 3-5)
  - Memberships and Associations - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1992-1996 (Box 91, Folder 6-10)
  - Reprints, 1962-1984 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Files - Reinventing America - Press Announcement, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Files - Staff Meeting - Lloyd N. Morrisett Talk, 1988 September-1991 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - 2017:FA785:001- Staff Meeting - Audio Tapes of Lloyd N. Morrisett's Talk re Program and Program Evaluation, 1988 September (Box 2017:FA785:001)
  - 2017:FA785:002- Staff Meeting - Audio Tapes of the April 21, 1989 and May 7, 1991 Meetings with Lloyd N. Morrisett, 1989 April 21; 1991 May 7 (Box 2017:FA785:002)
  - Administrative Files - Revision of Program Objectives, 1989 May (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Files - Markle Foundation Program Objectives 1994-1997 (Presented by Morrisett at the June 29, 1993 Board Meeting), 1993 June 29 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Files - Interactive Media, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Files - Universal Service - FCC Evaluation Meeting, 1997 August (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Administrative Files - Wireless Communications Filing Comments, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Administrative Files - Gubernick, Lisa (Morrisett Book 1996) (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Files - Siegel and Gale - Interactive Education Product, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Files - Leave Behind Project (Morrisett's Essays), 1997 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Files - Leave Behind Project - Board Dinner Speech, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Administrative Files - Patty Waters, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    Includes digital media.
  - Administrative Files - Chairman Project, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Administrative Files - Photo Project, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Administrative Files - Photo-Video Projects - Permission Forms, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Administrative Files - Video Project - Board Tribute, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Administrative Files - Video Project Phase I - Board Dinner, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Administrative Files - Markle Foundation - Publicity, 1972-1985 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Files - Grant Evaluations and Associated Reports and Publications, 1973-1997 (Box 92, Folder 2-13)
  - Administrative Files - Grant Evaluations and Associated Reports and Publications, 1975-1995 (Box 93, Folder 1-4)
- Financial records, 1950-1987; 5; 5.26 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes.
  Restricted material - financial records.
  - Tax Returns, Securities and Audits, 1950-1980 (Box 94)
  - Tax returns, securities and Audits, 1975-1979, 1983-1986 (Box 95)
  - Tax Returns, Federal, State and Quarterly, 1970-1975, 1979-1987 (Box 96)
  - Stocks and Bonds (Box 97)
    Restricted material - financial records
- Cathy Clark Files, 1989-1997; 6; 5.26 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes.
  - Democracy in America - Seminars and Events, 1991-1992 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Democracy in America - Programming, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Democracy in America - Voters' Channel, 1989-1992 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Democracy in America - School Utilization, 1991-1992 (Box 98, Folder 4-5)
  - Democracy in America - Evaluations of News Segments Broadcast on CNN, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 6-7)
  - Democracy in America - Evaluations of Specials Broadcast on CNN, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Democracy in America - Scripts of News Segments Broadcast on CNN, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 9-10)
  - Democracy in America - Scripts of Specials Broadcast on CNN, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 11-12)
  - Democracy in America - Final Report, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Foundation for American Communications (FACS) - Economics of the 1992 Elections - Briefing Manual (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - SeniorNet - Leadership Day, 1990 August 30 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Crossover - REUS (Reinventing America), 1995 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Crossover - REUS (Reinventing America), 1995 (Box 99, Folder 1-9)
  - REUS II (Reinventing America), 1996 (Box 99, Folder 10-15)
  - Wunderman Cato Johnson (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - REUS (Reinventing America) - Publicity, 1995-1996 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Crossover Technologies, 1994-1997 (Box 99, Folder 18-19)
  - Public Agenda Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 99, Folder 20-24)
  - Markle Foundation Roundtable - Meeting Preparation, 1993-1994 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - HomeNet, 1996-1997 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Lehman-Newell, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Homet, Ronald, 1992-1993 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Kimball, Richard, 1991-1994 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - SeniorNet, 1988-1995 (Box 100, Folder 6-18)
  - Northwestern University - Roger Schank Meetings (and Interactive Software Demonstration), 1996-1997 (Box 100, Folder 19-21)
  - Institute for the Learning Sciences, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Infonautics Corporation, 1993-1994 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Buchanan Conference, Washington, D.C., 1994 (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - 1996 Markle Commission, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - MAXIS, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - Markle Commission, 1988-1992 (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
  - Arlen Communications (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Buchanan Meeting, University of Texas, Austin, 1996 June 12-13 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1997 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Center for Governmental Studies, 1994-1998 (Box 101, Folder 7-9)
  - CNN, 1991-1994 (Box 101, Folder 10-24)
  - Owen Comora 1995 - Democracy in America, 1992-1997 (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - Contact Center Network, 1996-1997 (Box 101, Folder 26)
  - Chris Crawford Files, 1996-1998 (Box 101, Folder 27-35)
- Edith Bjornson Files, 1982-1998; 7; 30.23 Cubic Feet 23 standard record storage boxes
  Edith Bjornson served as and Executive Vice President and Senior Program Officer.
  Records primarily including media and election projects, general correspondence files, subject files, and reprints.
  - Markle Foundation Commission on the Media and the Electrorate - Report, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Markle Foundation Roundtable - The Future of Presidential Campaigns, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Markle Foundation Presidential Election Watch, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Alice Allen Communications, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 4-5)
  - Advertising Guidelines - MF-Crossover Online Games, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Adler, Richard (People and Technology) (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Public Agenda Foundation, 1989-1995 (Box 102, Folder 8-30)
    Including Electronic Town Meeting files.
  - PBS, 1989-1991 (Box 102, Folder 31-50)
    Includes files regarding The Voters Channel (TVC) and the Voters Voice (TVV) as well as discussion of political role and future strategies
  - PBS, 1990-1991 (Box 103, Folder 1-3)
    Includes files regarding The Voters Channel (TVC) and the Voters Voice (TVV) as well as the PBS Conference in Dallas Texas in May 1990.
  - Public Relations Firms - Reference File, 1989-1991 (Box 103, Folder 4-7)
  - Quick Tally Systems - Bleich, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Radio - American Public Radio, 1991-1992 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Radio - Minnesota Public Radio - Civic Journalism Initiative, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Radio - National Public Radio, 1989-1991 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Radio - Radio for Youth (Michael Pollack), 1991-1992 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - RAND - Tora Bickson, Lee Sproul, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - R/GA Interactive, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Reinventing America (REUS) - Issues, Design Responsibilities (Box 103, Folder 15-16)
  - Reinventing America (REUS) - Online Services, 1994-1995 (Box 103, Folder 17-22)
  - Reinventing America (REUS) - Publicity, Promotion, Marketing (Box 103, Folder 23-27)
  - Infornautics - Australian Information Network (AUSIENET), 1996 (Box 103, Folder 28)
  - Crossover Technologies, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 29-30)
  - TED Conferences - Richard Wurman (The Understanding Biz), 1990 (Box 103, Folder 31)
  - Tortorello, Nick, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 32)
  - TCI News, 1995-1997 (Box 103, Folder 33-35)
  - Thinking Tools - John Hiles, 1994-1996 (Box 103, Folder 36)
  - Thinking Tools - 1996 Election Project (Box 104, Folder 1-7)
  - Thinking Tools - SimHealth, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 8-12)
  - Thinking Tools - Race for the White House - Publicity, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Times Mirror Center Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 104, Folder 14-15)
  - 20th Century Fund - Task Force Report, 1992-1993 (Box 104, Folder 16-17)
  - IIA's Venture Forum, McGraw Hill Conference Center, 1997 February 5-6 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Video - Miscellaneous, 1982-1989 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Voyager Company Files, 1993-1997 (Box 104, Folder 20-35)
  - W-Z, 1990-1993 (Box 104, Folder 36-41)
  - WGBH (Boston) - Steve Atlas, 1990-1994 (Box 104, Folder 42)
  - WNYC, 1990-1995 (Box 104, Folder 43-46)
  - World - Miscellaneous, 1994-1997 (Box 104, Folder 47)
  - Daniel Yankelovich Studies and Conference Remarks, 1987-1988; 1997 (Box 104, Folder 48-49)
  - David Yespen, 1989-1991 (Box 104, Folder 50-51)
    Press Discussion, papers, and "Reporters Resource Center".
  - Weingarten, Rick, 1989-1991 (Box 104, Folder 52)
  - Westin, Alan (Columbia University) - Voice, Voter Online Information and Communication Exchange, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 53)
  - Zagat - Tortorello (Box 105, Folder 1-2)
  - Young and Rubicam (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Steve Zink (Box 105, Folder 4-7)
  - President's Essays (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Voyager - 1992 Fall Magazine (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - SeniorNet - Booklets (Box 105, Folder 10-11)
  - Markle Commission on the Media and the Electorate - Report, 1990 May (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Public Agenda Foundation (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous - M (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Markle Presidential Election Watch (Box 105, Folder 15-25)
  - James Marks - Body Health Resources Corp. (Box 105, Folder 26)
  - MAXIS (Box 105, Folder 27-37)
  - MAXIS - SimHealth - Washington Launch, 1993-1994 (Box 106, Folder 1-14)
  - E. Mickewicz - US-USSR Commission - Conferences and Attendees, 1990-1991 (Box 106, Folder 15-18)
  - New Hampshire - "Running Fair" - League of Women Voters, 1992 February 4 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - President '96 - Crossover - TSI, 1995-1996 (Box 106, Folder 20-27)
  - Monroe Price files, 1990-1996 (Box 106, Folder 28-38)
  - Advertising Online Guidelines, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Brookings Instititute - Ornstein and Mann, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - CD-ROM Producers, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Children's Television Network (CTW), 1994-1995 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Contact Center Network - Ami Dar, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Doe Coover, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Crossover Technologies - Bell Atlantic, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - CNN, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 8-10)
  - CSPAN - Jane Coleman, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Columbia University - Joan Konner proposal, 1993-1994 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Chris Crawford, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 13-14)
  - Doug Davis, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Bob Davidson, 1992-1997 (Box 107, Folder 16-18)
  - Rick Derman - Visit to Channel 9, 1993 November 30 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - John Diebold, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - DYG, Inc. (Formerly Yankelovich) - Annual Conferences, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Electronic Town Meetings - Meeting and Debrief, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 22-28)
  - Foundation for American Communications (FACS) - John E. Cox Jr., 1995 (Box 107, Folder 29)
  - James S. Fishkin, 1990-1994 (Box 107, Folder 30)
  - Game Developers, 1990-1991 (Box 107, Folder 31-33)
  - Greenberger, Martin (Multi-Media Roundtable), 1995 (Box 107, Folder 34)
  - Lisa Gubernick (MF Book), 1996 (Box 107, Folder 35)
  - Richard Heffner, 1988; 1995-1997 (Box 107, Folder 36-38)
  - Infonautics Corporation, 1992-1994 (Box 107, Folder 39)
  - Institute for the Study of Distributed Work (Charles Grantham), 1994 (Box 107, Folder 40)
  - Judith Keenan Communications, Inc. (Public Relations firm), 1996 (Box 107, Folder 41-42)
  - Life Plan Center (Gladys Thatcher), 1994-1995 (Box 107, Folder 43)
  - Frank Leicht, 1991-1993 (Box 107, Folder 44-48)
  - Markle Foundation - Performance Analysis and Operations Review Reports, 1987; 1988 (Box 107, Folder 49)
  - Alen Communications - Defining the Electronic Consumer II Conference, 1993 September 28-30 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous - A, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - American Museum of Natural History - Nancy Hechinger, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Archiving - Computer and Otherwise, 1997-1998 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Awards-Lectures File, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Agenda Set-Up, 1998 March (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Aspen, 1997-1998 (Box 108, Folder 8-16)
  - Alice Allen Communications, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Baird Book Material (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - B. Buchanan - 1998 June 12 Meeting - Presidential Election Study (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - Children's Internet Involvement - Frank Leicht, 1997 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous - B (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - Baird, Zoe (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - Patrick Barwise (London School of Business), 1998 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - Berkeley - Hal Varian, 1997 (Box 108, Folder 24)
  - Bernard, Lewis, 1996-1997 (Box 108, Folder 25)
  - Boston Library Group (Markle 70th Anniverary Book), 1996-1997 (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - Bellcore - Jim Katz, 1996-1997 (Box 108, Folder 27)
  - Brookings Instititute - Robert Crandall (Box 108, Folder 28)
  - Bruce Buchanan, 1997-1998 (Box 108, Folder 29-30)
  - Business Consultants (Box 108, Folder 31)
  - Business Plan Models, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 32)
  - Byron Preiss - Multimedia (Box 108, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous - C (Box 108, Folder 34)
  - China Program Exploration (Box 108, Folder 35)
  - Connecticut Public TV and Radio, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 36)
  - Center for Governmental Studies (Tracy Westen) (Box 108, Folder 37-38)
  - Center Miscellaneous - A-Z (Box 108, Folder 39)
  - Center for Democracy and Technology (Jerry Berman), 1997 (Box 108, Folder 40)
  - Center for Educational Technology (Box 108, Folder 41)
  - Center for Learning and Information (CLIN), 1995 (Box 108, Folder 42)
  - Carter Center, 1994-1998 (Box 108, Folder 43-46)
  - Center for Mass Media Research, University of Colorado at Boulder, 1994 (Box 108, Folder 47)
  - Center for Media and Public Affairs (Lichter), 1996-1998 (Box 108, Folder 48-51)
  - Children - General (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University - CITI - Media Studies Center - Future of Public Television, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University - CITI - Eli Noam (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Duke University - Commission on Radio and TV Policy (Ellen Mickiewicz), 1997 (Box 109, Folder 4-10)
  - Carter Commission (Box 109, Folder 11-12)
  - Duke University - Commission on Radio and TV Policy (Ellen Mickiewicz) (Box 109, Folder 13-16)
  - Owen Comora (Box 109, Folder 17-24)
  - Computer - Information-Education (Box 109, Folder 25)
  - Council - Miscellaneous - A-Z (Box 109, Folder 26)
  - Crawford, Kathleen, 1996 (Box 109, Folder 27)
  - Chris Crawford - Video Game Consultant (Box 109, Folder 28-33)
  - Crossover (Box 109, Folder 34-47)
  - Miscellaneous - D (Box 109, Folder 48)
  - Debit Cards (Box 109, Folder 49)
  - Digital TV Obligations (Box 109, Folder 50)
  - DYG Miscellaneous (Box 109, Folder 51)
  - Rick Derman - Website, 1996 (Box 109, Folder 52)
  - DKA, 1996 (Box 109, Folder 53-57)
  - Crossover - REUS (Reinventing America) II (Box 109, Folder 58-59)
  - Miscellaneous - S (Box 109, Folder 60)
  - Sandberg-Diment (Box 109, Folder 61-62)
  - Satellite Broadcast Network (SBN), 1987 (Box 109, Folder 63)
  - State of Democracy Meeting, 1993 April 20 (Box 109, Folder 64)
  - SeniorNet, 1993-1997 (Box 110, Folder 1-15)
  - Markle Foundation Performance Analysis Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 110, Folder 16-17)
  - Markle Foundation - Collected Reprints, 1942-1943 (Box 111)
    Reprints of articles published in 1942-1943 based on medical research supported wholly or in part by the Markle Foundation.
  - Markle Foundation - Collected Reprints, 1944-1946 (Box 112)
    Reprints of articles published in 1944-1946 based on medical research supported wholly or in part by the Markle Foundation.
  - Markle Foundation - Collected Reprints, 1946-1950 (Box 113)
    Reprints of articles published in 1946-1950 based on medical research supported wholly or in part by the Markle Foundation.
  - Public Broadcasting (PBS) - Restructuring, 1994-1996 (Box 114, Folder 1-9)
  - Crossover - Reinventing America (REUS) and the 1996 Presidential Election Project - Press - Promotion - Comora (Box 114, Folder 10-12)
  - SimHealth, Washington D.C., 1993 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Family - Money and Politics Report, 1990 April 1 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - TV Ratings Systems (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Lloyd N. Morrisett - Itineraries, Trips, 1996 December-1998 January (Box 114, Folder 16-50)
  - Articles - Artificial Intelligence, Virtual Reality, Creativity, Think Tanks, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 51-55)
  - Articles - General, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 56)
  - Articles - CNN - Press Releases and Publicity, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 57-59)
  - Articles - Communications, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 60)
  - Articles - Computer Rockefeller, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 61)
  - Articles - Computers - Accountability and Anti-Computer, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 62)
  - Articles - D, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 63-66)
  - Articles - Dupont Awards, 1990 January (Box 114, Folder 67)
  - Articles - E-H, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 68-70)
  - Articles - Education, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 71)
  - Articles - Election Project, 1995-1996 (Box 114, Folder 72-73)
  - Articles - Games - Electronic, Video, and Homework Helper, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 74-75)
  - Articles - Elections, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 76-85)
  - Articles - Electronic and Email, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 86-89)
  - Articles - Health Care, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 90-92)
  - Articles - I-L, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 93-96)
  - Articles - Interactivity, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 97-98)
  - Articles - Internet, World Wide Web, 1990s (Box 114, Folder 99-100)
  - Articles - M-Z, 1990s (Box 115, Folder 1-13)
  - Articles - Markle Foundation, 1990s (Box 115, Folder 14-17)
  - Articles - Networks and Network News, 1990s (Box 115, Folder 18-20)
  - Articles - On-Line Services, 1990s (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Articles - Politically Correct, 1990s (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Articles - Press, 1990s (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Articles - Public, 1990s (Box 115, Folder 24-26)
  - Articles - W-Z, 1990s (Box 115, Folder 27-28)
  - Officers and Associates - CVs (Box 115, Folder 29-37)
  - Fred Ritchin (New York University) (Box 115, Folder 38)
  - Stanley Rothman - Smith College - University of Mass at Northampton, 1993-1996 (Box 115, Folder 39-40)